DEB JOHNSON

PRODUCT DESIGNER

SKILLS

UX DESIGN

USER RESEARCH

USER TESTING

PROTOTYPING

HTML/CSS

TOOLS

SKETCH

AFFINITY DESIGNER

INVISION

603-738-0035 deb@debjohnson.design http://debjohnson.design

ABOUT

I'm a product designer and front-end developer (HTML/CSS) with a passion for user-centered design. I specialize in user experience design, user research, prototyping, and user testing. I'm passionate about building products that have a meaningful impact on people's everyday lives.

EXPERIENCE

Tradecraft

PRODUCT DESIGNER

SAN FRANCISCO, CA MAY 2017 - PRESENT

 Full-time design apprenticeship program that prepares individuals to excel at high-growth startups through a combination of hands-on projects work for startups, curriculum, and mentorship from industry practitioners.

Neon Labs

PRODUCT DESIGNER

SAN FRANCISCO, CA FEB. 2013 - APRIL 2016

- Established company's design process and best practices
- Conducted user research to validate product directions; explored UI concepts with rapid prototyping and user testing
- Designed analytics dashboard to display A/B testing data;
 Collaborated with engineers to build prototype
- Designed internal tool to search through thousands of images generated by product

Neon Labs

FOUNDING TEAM MEMBER

SAN FRANCISCO, CA FEB. 2012 - FEB 2013

- Member of founding team; helped craft early product vision, performed customer discovery to find product market fit
- Helped define company culture, vision, and values
- Worked directly with CEO to design pitch decks that helped raise over \$8M in venture funding

EDUCATION

Dartmouth College

B.A. Psychology, Music

HANOVER, NH 2006 - 2010